Welcome back y'all, this is the Amanda Seals Show, it's your girl Amanda Seals, your favorite comedian and common sense specialist, but we are joined by another favorite comedian, Thelonious Ma.
We're talking about some relationships, we're talking about spinning the block.
You're asking me to take a chance with my own heart when the only evidence that I have of you being a different person is you saying it, right?
Like I shot a man a bunch of times because he robbed me.
Now, he doesn't owe me anything, the last time I saw him he was, I didn't, I shot him six times, he ain't gotta forgive me is what, no, but, but, but, and see that's the thing, most of the people who know me since can't imagine that person, they don't know that person exists, they don't have to forgive me because I've never done that to them.
And so they treat me as the person that I am.
If I bumped into him, I don't get to say, do you know what I've done for Palestine?
Do you know what I've done to raise money for the queer community?
Do you know how, what I've done for the trans, do you know how I've done for black men and black women?
I know what you did to me and that's fair.
And I think when we're spinning the block, we're forgetting that we've done damage to people.
We are...